Guide to the Charles L. Adams Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Frank Waters Society, 1975-2002; Series IV; 4.42 linear feet (6 boxes)
  - Studies in Frank Waters XIX - Insights, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 420)
  - Centenial Celebration, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 421)
  - Frank Waters Foundation - Taos, New Mexico, medallion (Box 36, Folder 725)
    This box contains a bronze medallion of Frank Waters, created by Mark Rossi, a Tucson sculptor.
- General and Teaching Files, 1960-2000; Series V; 10.42 linear feet (11 boxes)
  This series consists of files stemming from Adams's teaching and academic activities and relating to his tenure as a Professor at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas. While there is nothing to suggest that Adams's had any sort of filing system per se, these files were foldered and labeled by Adams and seem to be have been kept more or less as a group. Files include university related catalogs and material, class and student papers, general seminar information and records, day calendars, Adams' curriculum vitae and general academic material, especially scattered correspondence and notes.
  Arranged in rough chronological order.
  - University of Nevada - Class Schedule, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 422)
  - University of Nevada - Catalogs and Schedules, 1962-1971 (Box 19, Folder 423)
  - University of Nevada - Class Schedule, 1963-1967 (Box 19, Folder 424)
  - University of Nevada - Catalogs, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 425)
  - Murphy, Sharon, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 426)
  - Kohn, Willa, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 427)
  - University of Nevada - Catalogs, 1969-1970s (Box 19, Folder 428)
  - By Laws - College of Arts and Letters, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 429)
  - Constanten, Thomas, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 430)
  - English Department, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 431)
  - Frank Waters Students, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 432)
  - Taos and the Southwest, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 433)
  - University of Nevada, Las Vegas, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 434-437)
    Include catalogs, clippings and photocopies.
  - Unused Notes for Chapter, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 438)
  - Visual, photographs, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 439)
  - Yogi, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 440)
  - Aniello, Robert, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 441)
  - Duplicates, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 442-443)
    Includes a copy of New Mexico Magazine, 1971, as well as a copy of East West Magazine, 1977.
  - Frank Waters, seminar writing, 1970s-1980s (Box 19, Folder 444)
  - Rocky Mountain Modern Language Association (RMMLA)
    - 1970s-1977 1970s-1977 (Box 20, Folder 445-448)
    - 1977-1987 1977-1987 (Box 21, Folder 449-471)
    - 1988-2002 1988-2002 (Box 22, Folder 472-485)
  - Tailings from thr Pike's Peak Lode: I, 1970s-1980s (Box 22, Folder 486)
  - University of Nevada, Las Vegas, 1970s-1990s (Box 22, Folder 487)
  - Blue Lake, Sacked Mtns, etc. (etc!), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 488)
  - Class Exams, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 489-492)
  - Pike's Peak + Spring 1971 (Box 22, Folder 493)
  - Frank Waters (Spring '73 Class), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 494)
  - From Files of Edgely Todd, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 495)
  - Psych Today (May '73), 'A Conversation with Frank Waters', 1973 (Box 22, Folder 496)
  - Anaya, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 497)
  - Givens, Bridgett Ann, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 498)
  - Visual (Class), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 499)
  - FW - Grant Print Outs, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 500)
  - Allen, Harvey, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 501)
  - Brett, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 502)
  - Day Calendar, notes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 503)
  - FW Sem 75 - II, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 504-505)
  - Misc. Lecture Material, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 506)
  - Music, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 507)
  - Rem Tech 75, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 508)
  - Frank Waters Seminar 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 509)
  - Woman At Otowi Crossing, 1975-1980s (Box 23, Folder 510)
  - A.E., clippings, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 511)
  - March 31, 1976 - Sedona Notes From Hotel Room (Box 23, Folder 512)
  - Waters Seminar - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 513)
  - Swallow Press, 1976-1982 (Box 23, Folder 514)
  - FW Grant Requests, 1976-1986 (Box 23, Folder 515)
  - People of the Valley, 1976-1986 (Box 23, Folder 516)
  - Shasky and Stanford Project, 1976-1988 (Box 23, Folder 517)
  - Day Calendar, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 518)
  - Earp Brothers, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 519)
  - Mosaic, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 520)
  - Tele-lecture, Jan '77, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 521)
  - Time Sheets, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 522)
  - Vitae, 1977-1994 (Box 24, Folder 523-537)
  - Waters Seminar, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 538)
  - Daley, Pat, 1977-1986 (Box 24, Folder 539)
  - Grattan, Carolyn, 1977-1981 (Box 24, Folder 540)
  - BANFF, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 541)
  - Cuchama, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 542-543)
  - Day Calendar, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 544)
  - FW Sem. MLA 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 545)
  - University Musical Society, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 546)
  - SNTE, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 547)
  - Anderson, Bob, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 548)
  - Carey, Kathryn D., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 549)
  - Day Calendar, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 550)
  - FW MLA Nomination, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 551)
  - Reno Workshop - Nov 79, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 552)
  - Taos 31 Jul - 7 Aug 1979 (Box 25, Folder 553)
  - Frank Waters Seminars, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 554)
  - Campbell, Felicia Florine, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 555-556)
  - Taos - 12 Aug 1980 (Box 25, Folder 557)
  - University of Nevada, Las Vega - Office of Financial Aid, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 558)
  - Chronology, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 559)
  - ISBN Log, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 560)
  - "The Man Who Killed the Deer", 1980 (Box 25, Folder 561)
  - Xerographic Label Sheet, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 562)
  - Patrick and FW Course, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 563)
  - Adams, Rebecca, 1980s (Box 25, Folder 564)
  - Byrns, Richard, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 565)
  - Sabbat 1980, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 566)
  - Evaluations and Grant / Vita, 1980-1990s (Box 25, Folder 567)
  - Glenn, Robert J., Jr., 1980-1990s (Box 25, Folder 568)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1980-1990s (Box 25, Folder 569-572)
  - Cuchama, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 573-574)
    Includes photographic slides.
  - Day Calendar, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 575)
  - FW - May 1981-UNLV (Box 25, Folder 576)
  - FW - Las Vegas 19-22 Nov 1981 (Box 25, Folder 577)
  - Frank Waters and The Moment for Right Action, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 578)
  - Frank Waters' Portrait, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 579)
    Includes a photographic portrait of Frank Waters, taken at the home of John Manchester, Las Vegas, on 24 May 1981. The photograph is by Dick Gueder, and was taken one day after Frank Waters had delievered the University of Nevada, Las Vegas Commencement Address.
  - Frank Waters' 'Prelude To Change' - NHSQ, commencement address, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 580-583)
  - Hambley, Gail, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 584)
  - Mountain Dialogues, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 585-586)
  - Review of Milton's Norel, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 587)
  - Stanford Visit (May 81), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 588)
  - Barrick Travel, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 589)
  - Cuchama, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 590)
  - Day Calendar, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 591-592)
  - Forgotten Testimony... Phoenix, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 593)
  - FW - MLA - 1982 (Box 26, Folder 594)
  - Mary Colter Review, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 595)
  - Mystic Tailings - MLA, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 596)
  - Pike's Peak (Bontta Denver), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 597)
  - T2 Bib - Review, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 598)
  - Taos and AIBQ, including photographs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 599)
  - Tucson, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 600)
  - FW Reader Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 601)
  - On Waters: A-Z, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 602-605)
  - The Brumble Rumble, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 606)
  - Cuchama, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 607)
  - Day Calendar, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 608)
  - FW's 'Symbols and Sacred Mountains, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 609)
  - San Diego, March 1983 (Box 27, Folder 610)
  - Senior Citizen Center, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 611)
  - Tucson, January 1983 (Box 27, Folder 612)
  - University of Nevada, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 613)
  - Interdisc. Comm., 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 614)
  - A.T.A.I. Mehto Park, CA, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 615)
  - Copyright Material, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 616)
  - The Desert Rose - Rev., 1984 (Box 27, Folder 617)
  - Masked Gods, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 618)
  - Storytelling Cont., 1984 (Box 27, Folder 619)
  - British Association of American Studies, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 620)
  - Colorado Springs, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 621)
  - FW Reader, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 622)
  - Old Addresses, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 623)
  - Photographs, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 624)
  - Tailings From The Pike's Peak Load, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 625)
  - Toast... Ripples, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 626)
  - A.A.S.C. - April, 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 627-629)
  - APL, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 630)
  - Nobel Prize, 1985-1994 (Box 27, Folder 631-639)
  - The Blind Coral, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 640)
  - Flight From Fiesta, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 641)
  - Modes of Perception in F.W., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 642)
  - Phoenix Magazine, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 643)
  - Sturdevant, Katherine Scott, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 644)
  - Utah - 30 Jul-1 Aug 86, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 645)
  - Campbell vs. UNS et Al., 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 646)
  - FW's The Colorado - Kingman, AZ, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 647)
  - The Genesis of 'Flight From Fiesta', 1987 (Box 28, Folder 648)
  - Henderson - English 223, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 649)
  - Life Amongst The Modoes - Review, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 650)
  - National School Board Association, '76, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 651)
  - Retirement, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 652)
  - Sacajawea, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 653)
  - Visual Class Selections, including photographic slides, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 654)
  - Campbell, Felicia, 1987-1991 (Box 28, Folder 655)
  - Green, Michael S., 1988 (Box 28, Folder 656)
  - Kostka Interview, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 657)
  - Reno Workshop: Nov. 1988 (Box 28, Folder 658)
  - Undergraduate Studies Comm., 1988 (Box 28, Folder 659)
  - English Department, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 660)
  - Arts and Letters, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 661)
  - Berkeley, July 1989, including photographs (Box 28, Folder 662)
  - Far West - American Culture, Jan. 1989 (Box 28, Folder 663)
  - Keene, Roberta E., 1989 (Box 28, Folder 664)
  - R.R. Bowker - ISBN and LC, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 665)
  - Cross Reference: Woman at Otowi Crossing, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 666)
  - FWAC / FWPC, Jan 1990 (Box 28, Folder 667)
  - Abbey, Rita, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 668)
  - Blackburn, Alex", writings and clippings., 1990s (Box 28, Folder 669-670)
  - Colorado Springs, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 671-672)
  - English 460 - Exam #3, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 673)
  - English A, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 674)
  - Frost - 'Away', 1990s (Box 28, Folder 675)
  - Frost - 'Away', 1990s (Box 29, Folder 676-677)
  - Lloyd, Susan, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 678)
  - St. Louis - Opera / Otowi, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 679)
  - Various English Stories, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 680-682)
  - WVU - Morgantown, Oct 1990, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 683)
  - English 440, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 684)
  - FW's 'The One Great Book of Life, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 685)
  - Gordon, Lilias, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 686)
  - Student Evaluation of Reader: Gloria Jones, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 687)
  - PPCA and ACA, Nov 1993 Phila. (Box 29, Folder 688)
  - Wilderness Conference, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 689)
  - The Lost World, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 690-691)
    Includes writing and teaching material relating to Sir Auther Conan Doyle's "The Lost World".
  - WVU, Sept-Oct 1994 (Box 29, Folder 692)
  - FWPCA / FWACA, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 693-694)
  - Update, 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 695)
  - Grammar Worksheets, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 696)
  - WVU - Otowi Opera, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 697)
  - Retirement, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 698)
  - Clark, Gabe, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 699)
  - Frank Waters Keynote, undated (Box 29, Folder 700)
  - Frank Waters Luncheon, undated (Box 29, Folder 701-703)
  - Mexico Mystique, undated (Box 29, Folder 704)
  - Pumpkin Seedpoint, undated (Box 29, Folder 705)
  - To Possess The Land, undated (Box 29, Folder 706)
- Audiovisual Material, circa 1970-2000; Series VI; 3.42 linear feet (4 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Audio
    Other Finding Aids
    An item list of audiocassettes can be found within each box.
    - Frank Waters Related, audiocassettes (Box 30)
      Includes sound recordings of interviews, seminars, lectures, readings and other events featuring or relating to Frank Waters. It also holds folders 707-710.
      - Sedona copy no. 2, 1975 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396128)
        A note with the audiocassette has a description that reads: Waters on Lyons.
      - "Past as Prologue in Col Sp.", copy, 1981 July 9; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396136)
      - Sedona copy no. 1, 1975 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396144)
      - Sedona copy no. 4, 1975 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396151)
      - Sedona copy no. 3, 1975 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396169)
      - Taos copy no. III, 1975 July; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396177)
      - Taos copy no. II, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396185)
      - Taos copy no. I, 1975 July; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396193)
      - Seminar, San Francisco, copy, 1975 December; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396201)
      - Sedona copy no. I, 1976 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396219)
      - Sedona copy no. II, 1976 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396227)
      - Sedona, copy no. III, 1976 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396235)
      - pre and post EW discussion with Frank Waters, Pat and CA, Sedona, copy, 1976 March; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396243)
      - Tucson copy no. II, side 1 only, 1977 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396250)
      - Tucson copy no. I, 1977 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396268)
      - RMMLA seminar, tape no. 1, copy no. 2, 1979 October; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396276)
      - Manchester, tape no. 1, copy, 1976 October; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396284)
      - Taos, Frank Waters and Krutch, copy no. II, 1976 September; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396292)
      - Manchester, talk and piano, tape no. 2, copy, 1976 October; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396300)
      - RMMLA seminar, Denver, copy, 1980 October 18; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396318)
      - RMMLA seminar, side one only, copy no. II, 1977 October; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396326)
      - RMMLA seminar copy no. I, 1977 October 20; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396334)
      - Taos copy no. I, 1976 September 2; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396342)
      - Sedona, Pers. copy no. II, 1976 March; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396359)
      - MT Lobo, Tape I, copy, 1980 August 14; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396367)
      - MT Lobo, Tape II, copy, 1980 August 14; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396375)
      - Adams (Karen Jensen questions on Pike's Peak and Bob. A), Tucson, original, 1982 February 6; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396383)
      - Bob A., Tucson, second tape, original, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396391)
      - Bob A + FW: Tucson, Tape I, original, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396409)
      - Seminar - RMMLA, Bob's Tape, original no. 2, 1979; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396417)
      - Seminar, RMMLA, Bob's Tape, original no. 1, 1979; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396425)
      - Tucson, original, 1980 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396433)
      - Tucson, tape no. 1, copy, 1979 April 10; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396441)
      - Seminar, RMMLA, Denver, original, 1980 October 18; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396458)
      - Ban[?] and Rudy Wiehe, original, 1978 April 12; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396466)
      - Vegas, original from Judy, tape no. 1, 1978 April 11; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396474)
      - MT Lobo, (question period), tape no. 2, original, 1980 August 14; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396482)
      - MT Lobo, tape no. 1, original, 1980 August 14; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396490)
      - RMMLA seminar, original, 1979 October 20; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396508)
        This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate.
      - RMMLA seminar, tape no. 2, original, 1979 October; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396516)
      - Frank Waters reading Pike's Peak, RMMLA, Denver, original, 1980 October 17; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396524)
      - Tucson, Tape I, original, 1979 April 10; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396532)
      - Tucson, Tape II, original, 1979 April 10; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396540)
      - Tucson, original, 1981 January 24; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396557)
      - Vegas, tape no. 2, original from Judy R., 1978 April 11; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396565)
      - "Past as Prologue", Pikes Peak Library District, Colorado Springs, 1981 July 9; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396573)
      - Dick Harrison in Frank Waters' class, Tape II, 1980 April 21; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396581)
      - Dick Harrison in Frank Waters' class, Tape I, 1980 April 21; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396599)
      - Tucson, copy, 1980 January; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396607)
      - RMMLA seminar, Albuquerque, Bob's tape, no. 2, 1979; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396615)
      - RMMLA seminar, Albuquerque, Bob's tape, no. 1, copy, 1979; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396623)
      - Stanford, tape II, copy II, 1976 March; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396631)
      - Stanford, tape I, copy I, 1976 March; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396649)
      - Tucson, copy, 1981 January 24; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396656)
      - MLA seminar notes, original, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396664)
      - Stanford II, second copy, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396672)
      - Stanford II, EW copy, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396680)
      - 440 MM, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396698)
      - Friday / Monday 27th, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396706)
      - 4-8 Wednesday / Friday, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396714)
      - Untitled, undated; 1; The audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396722)
      - Monday 23 / Wednesday 25, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396730)
      - Friday, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396748)
      - W (22) A / 7-B (24), undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396755)
      - Wednesday, April 1 / Friday, April 3 / Monday, April 6, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396763)
      - A: Frank Waters Lec., undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396771)
      - A. + Pat in Sedona, 1976 March 31; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396789)
      - Wednesday, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396797)
      - Friday / Monday / Wednesday, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396805)
      - Monday / Wednesday, March 16; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396813)
      - Monday / Wednesday, April 1; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396821)
      - 2 A only, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396839)
      - Friday, March; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396847)
      - Friday, 20 / Monday, 23, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396854)
      - 440 Wednesday, undated; 1 (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396862)
      - Andy D. A. Tape, copied, undated; 1; The audiotape reel is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 30, Item barcode 39002091396870)
    - Frank Waters Related, audiocassettes (Box 31)
      Box 31 includes audiocassettes filed in folders 711-714. Folder 715 holds two empty cassette cases.
      - Untitled, undated; 1; A note attached to the audiocassette reads: 7 hours, original. (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394925)
      - Tucson, original, 1988 March 7; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394933)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394941)
      - National Public Radio, 1990; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394958)
      - Barff / Rudy Wiebe, 1978 April 12; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394966)
      - "Symbols and Sacred Mountains", UNLV, 1981 November 21; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394974)
      - Group interview, UNLV, 1987 March 20; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394982)
      - Frank Water's class, 1981 November 20; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091394990)
      - FWPCA seminar, 1992 February 8; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395013)
      - FWPCA seminar, 1992 February 8; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395005)
      - FWPCA seminar, 1992 February 8; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395054)
      - NPR, Morning Edition, 1995 June 15; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395021)
      - NPR, Morning Edition, 1995 June 15; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395112)
      - "Symbols and Sacred Mountains", UNLV, 1981 November 21; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395039)
        This audiocassette may be a duplicate.
      - "Symbols and Sacred Mountains", UNLV, copy, 1981 November 21; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395096)
      - FWPCA seminar, original, 1996; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395070)
      - FWPCA seminar, copy, 1996 February; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395047)
      - UNLV, copy, 1987 March 20; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395062)
        Runtime: 60 minutes
      - FWPCA seminar, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395088)
      - UNLV 18th Commencement, "Prelude to Change", duplicate, 1981 May 23; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395104)
      - American Prose Library interview, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395120)
      - Tucson, copy, 1988 March 7; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395138)
      - Discussion with Frank Waters, Henderson Campus CCCC, 1985 November 23; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395146)
      - Discussion with Frank Waters, Henderson Campus CCCC, copy, 1985 November 23; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395153)
      - Vegas, tape 1, copy 2, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395302)
      - Vegas, tape 2, copy 2, 1978 April; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395161)
      - Writing the Southwest by David Dunaway, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395179)
      - Reading from Deer, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395187)
      - Western American Writers, "The Works of Frank Waters", lecturer Thomas Lyon, 1974; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395195)
        Runtime: 35 minutes.
      - Reading from The Man Who Killed the Deer, American Audio Prose Library, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395203)
        Runtime: 40 minutes, mono
      - Tucson, tape 2, copy, 1979 April 10; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395211)
      - Stanford University, E-W lecture, copy, 1981 May 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395229)
      - Stanford University, E-W lecture, "Symbols and Sacred Mountains", copy, 1981 May 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395237)
      - K. Jensen's questions on Pk's Pk, Tucson, copy, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395245)
      - Tucson, copy 1, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395260)
      - Tucson, copy 2, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395252)
      - Western Literature Association, Conversations on Frank Waters (T. Lyon, B. Kostka, J. Milton, G. Rogers), Reno, Nevada, 1992 October 9; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395278)
      - Frank Waters, Bob A, CA, Tucson, 1st tape, copy 2, 1982 February 5; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395286)
        A note reads: first part is missing, see other tape 1.
      - American Audio Prose Library, interview, undated; 1 (Box 31, Item barcode 39002091395294)
        Recorded in mono.